In a future where humankind has moved into space,
our great effort becomes a song.
The tears we shed become stars.
AKB-0048, we will fly through space to see you.
What do you want?
Stop!
Get out of our way!
What kind of gathering do you think you're going to?
Who knows?
Don't play dumb!
Associating with the Earth is a serious crime.
Come on, show me your IDs!
Don't be ridiculous!
Don't resist!
Sit down!
Come on!
You're being a big woman!
Get out!
Don't be so ridiculous!
Shh!
What's wrong?
Nothing.
It's probably just a mouse.
That was close.
I thought my heart was going to jump out of my chest.
Here!
Wow, Yuko.
You're so thoughtful.
Nagisa!
Oh!
Anyway, Chiri, our live performance is really that amazing?
You'll understand soon.
It's incredible.
You won't forget once you see it in person.
What?
I'm scared.
Oh, Orine.
It's okay.
I'm here!
They're here!
Oh!
Wow!
They're here!
That must be them!
Yeah!
Oh!
Aida arises
AidaAKI
Is ruling the man
Oh so this is entertainment
Soriné? I feel so weird! Why is that?
Oh, wow!
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
They're angels!
I want to some
No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. Oh, oh, oh, oh!
I want to any such good guesses I'll do.
Oh, no, no, no
Oh, yeah!
I am this dude!
Yeah!
Multiple objects have appeared on radar.
It's a DES unmanned attack force.
They're finally here.
Increase the barrier's strength immediately.
Guardian Angels, ready for launch.
Takamina!
Marika-sama!
They're not just coming from above.
The riot police are approaching too.
Up for an entourage?
Got it!
Higherly.
Shocked!
Oh, now!
Yeah, user!
Yeah, yeah!
Yes!
All right!
It's show time!
Boom.
Oh, my heart is pounding.
The music is good!
It's singing in time with the music.
It's here to that.
It's shouting in time with the music.
Oh!
I don't know when to give up!
I can't hold it back anymore!
Takamina, if we keep this up, the fans got it!
Let's finish this song!
What is this song?
Oh!
Bye-bye!
I... I definitely want to be a part of AKB0048.
Me too!
No matter how long it's been, the memory of that concert and those songs are still with me.
Everyone was filled with so much happiness.
It was really wonderful.
It was a while ago, but I'll never forget them.
I have missed you!
Yes!
Even on a planet with a long-standing performing arts band like ours, due to the guerrilla concert of idol group AKB0048 ten years ago, voices demanding performing arts enrich their lives...
...and their performing arts have increased...
Under certain conditions, some performances have been...
Look!
Huh? What's wrong, Wurumiya?
Huh?
Get back in your seat.
Oh! Yes, sir.
Oh!
Ornay-chan works so hard.
That girl doesn't have anyone to take care of her.
And she's only 13 years old.
Ornay-chan, we're done for the day.
We're done for the day.
Have you gotten used to it yet, dear?
Oh, yes.
Some of it is still a little difficult,
but I enjoy tinkering with the machines.
It's fun.
Is that right?
Yes.
Why don't you take this with you?
I'm sorry, they're just leftovers.
Thank you very much.
I'll eat them later.
My phone.
I'm so sorry.
I'll set it to silence.
Yuka, should we do this now?
Hold on, I'm looking for the audition home page right now.
Hey.
Don't touch it with your sticky hands!
Sorry.
Here, this is it.
Let's see.
0048!
What?
Hello, I'm AKB0048's fifth generation Taka Hashimina.
Orine, it's Takamina!
Don't look away!
Okay.
Let's keep watching, then.
We have decided to recruit our 77th generation of trainees to join our group.
We're idols who go to see our audience.
Even if the planet has an entertainment band,
we'll be there to deliver music to our fans.
AKB0048 pays its respects to the founding AKB members
by taking on their names and carrying on their legacy.
You might even be able to take on the name of the girl you look up to!
If you're lucky...
It's Yuko!
We saw her at the concert!
Wow, Yuko's really grown up!
You're one to talk!
We're waiting to hear about you!
We want to meet your smile, girl!
Applicants from planets with entertainment bands
can send their data to be checked.
Just be safe and make sure you protect your data before sending it.
What should we do?
How should I know?
Well, I'm going to apply!
Nagisa!
The Yuko we saw then is saying she wants us to come and meet her!
So we don't have a choice!
Remember your wishes can come true
But that first step can only be taken by you
And after all the rain
The sun will shine on you again
Yuko, that was great!
Yeah, you sounded kind of like Mayu-yuu
Really?
Okay, now it's your turn, Nagisa!
Oh, okay!
I have missed you!
Yeah!
Huh?
I have missed you!
Yeah!
Oh!
Sorry!
I'm not used to singing!
I got embarrassed!
Nagisa!
What are you talking about?
You'll never be accepted like that!
But I could tell you're motivated!
Really?
All right!
Oh, give me a break!
That was pretty sad!
Well, I'm sure all I need is some practice!
Looks like my turn next!
What are we going to do if we actually pass the audition, huh?
I would succeed Mari Kusama!
I'd like to succeed!
Sashiii, I guess!
What?
You're nothing like her!
Sorry!
Gotta go!
I'll see you guys later!
Hmm?
What are you doing?
Are you practicing?
Yeah!
The tournament's coming up!
Hmm!
Will you get to play?
Maybe!
Is he Yuka's boyfriend?
She said they're not dating yet!
Hey!
Adikata is a song about telling the one you love how you feel, right?
Mm-hmm!
The one that you love!
I wonder what exactly it would be like to love someone like that!
You think Yuka and that boy have kissed?
What?
Kissed?
It's nothing to be embarrassed about!
I could even kiss you, Oine!
What?
I-I can't!
I can't!
He was just kidding!
Sensei, Sensei.
The thoughts of these young girls have traveled through space.
Please give us your holy lyrics.
If you keep eating so many tomatoes, your face is going to turn all red.
But I like tomatoes.
Nagisa?
Yeah, Dad?
You seem to have put an entertainment poster in your room.
You went in there without asking me?
Entertainment hasn't been fully accepted on this planet yet.
Take the poster down.
What?
It was really hard to get that.
I'll apply for permission and-
Also, you were singing in your room just now.
People will talk if they find out someone was singing in an entertainment administrator's house.
Don't do it anymore.
Thanks for the food.
Nagisa!
Leave the girl.
Oh!
Ugh.
Stupid.
Stupid, Dad!
They're so cute.
I wonder if I could become an idol like them.
Nagisa!
I'm coming in.
I wish I could wear a cute scrunchie like that.
They're awesome.
Nagisa!
Oh, Mom!
Eat these.
Your father was just promoted to a department head at the Entertainment Bureau.
He can't stop thinking about the entertainment laws right now.
I don't care about that!
It's his fault I'm bad at singing.
He always gets mad if I sing at home,
and I couldn't practice outside because of my curfew.
Nagisa, try to understand how your father feels.
What about my feelings?
What about them?
Nagisa.
You're on...
You're on Dad's side.
Don't forget to put away your dishes.
I don't want rice balls you made.
Oh no.
This is crazy!
What's wrong, Yucca?
We...
We made it past the first training!
Who did?
We halted!
Look! We even got electronic tickets to the venue!
This is amazing! I can't believe all three of us passed! It's like a dream!
Right, Nagisa?
I might not be able to go.
Huh?
I just can't.
What? But you're the one who said we should do it!
You said Zero Zero was waiting for us!
I know, and I'm happy I passed.
But it's no secret my father will never let me go with you.
And you know I'm not confident in my singing ability.
There's no way I'd pass.
Nagisa!
Why are you getting scared now?
You're so lame! Cowards are so lame!
Lame, lame, lame, lame!
Wait! Yuka!
Dad, can we talk?
I got asked to try out...
to sing.
No!
Why not?
It wouldn't be strange if the Anti-Entertainment Extremist Army D.E.S. attacked the audition.
But...
There's no reason for you to pointlessly put yourself in danger.
Pointless.
Honey...
Now let's go.
0048 came to see us.
Four years ago,
when this planet still had a complete entertainment ban.
They must have known it was dangerous,
but...
but they still came to see us!
Nagisa,
I said no.
Because of that concert that day,
this planet was changed!
Changed for the better!
What need is there to change?
Nagisa!
Leave her.
What's wrong with dreaming, huh?
It's not like I have passed yet!
But you're going because you want to pass, right?
I...
I love you.
If you pass your audition and become an idol,
I don't think I'll be able to love you anymore.
And that's all there is to it.
I guess that's it.
Have a nice life, Yuka.
I'm definitely gonna pass.
You watch me.
And when I become a member of 0048,
I won't give you my autograph!
Yuka.
I'll clean now.
I really loved this place.
The truth is,
I wanted to go to school with Nagisa and Yuka.
Everyone here was so nice to me.
I managed to forget
my sadness and everything.
Some day,
when the cherry blossoms bloom,
let's meet here again!
Yuka's right.
I'm afraid of getting hurt.
Yuka...
got hurt.
My...
our dream.
The dream that started here.
I...
What is she doing?
Is she asleep?
You'll catch a cold if you sleep out here, Nagisa.
Wake up!
She's hopeless.
Is Nagisa really not gonna audition with us?
I wonder what she's gonna do.
Yeah.
Joining AKB wasn't my dream at all.
Huh?
I mean...
joining AKB with you and Nagisa was.
I was supposed to just be pretending to sleep.
But I eventually ended up actually falling asleep.
And I saw Yuka and Orine singing as members of AKB-00 on that stage.
I thought they were beautiful as they sang and danced.
I'm not there.
Because...
That's where we're going!
Uh-huh!
Way out there!
The poster I gave up on.
An empty place.
A space that can't be filled.
After all...
I...
Nagisa!
Mom!
Um...
I...
What is it?
Huh?
What?
This is...
What do you think?
It's like the one in the poster!
Sorry.
I was kind of in a hurry, so it might not be very well made.
Oh, Mom!
Thanks, Mom!
You're out!
I wonder where she is.
Forget her.
She's a coward.
What?
I love this town.
Where is Nagisa?
She's probably still asleep.
I see.
I love dad and mom.
And?
No.
I love AKZ.
I love zero zero 48.
I love dad.
Oh?
What?
Oh!
Run!
Ragnarok!
Yuka!
I'm so glad you made it, Nagisa!
Oh god, you really scared me!
Let's go together!
Toward our dream!
Episode 4
Thank you.
I can't believe Chieri's missing.
She does.
I'm sure she hasn't forgotten her dream.
Come on.
Let's go.